{
    "subject": "resource/Hierarchical_Cluster_Engine_Project",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/C++",
    "human_readable": "The Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project was developed using C++.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8916343450546265,
            "question": "Are there any known limitations of using C++ for the Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.820277988910675,
            "question": "What programming language was used to develop the Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6925532221794128,
            "question": "Can you describe the nature of the Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6726616024971008,
            "question": "What are some potential applications of a Hierarchical Cluster Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6582222580909729,
            "question": "What are some future developments or enhancements that could be made to the Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6230576038360596,
            "question": "How does the Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project contribute to the field of data science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5759061574935913,
            "question": "What is the name of the project that utilized C++?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3680543005466461,
            "question": "What are the advantages of using C++ for this type of project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26316821575164795,
            "question": "Besides C++, are there any other programming languages involved in this project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1797330379486084,
            "question": "Is C++ a suitable language for developing complex data processing systems?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project was developed using C++.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8305_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides C++, are there any other programming languages involved in this project?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8305_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the advantages of using C++ for this type of project?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8305_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the project that utilized C++?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8305_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8305_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The HCE project aim and main idea mention that the solution can be built on C++ language, which implies that the Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project was developed using C++."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the HCE project is built on a C++ language foundation, which supports the query \"The Hierarchical Cluster Engine Project was developed using C++.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}